affirm.com 2015-04-03

# Affirm | Privacy Policy

###### Last Updated December 13, 2018

PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY. THIS POLICY DESCRIBES THE WAYS Affirm, INC. (“Affirm”, “we”, “us”, “our”) OR OUR VENDORS COLLECT, PROTECT, USE AND STORE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION. YOU ACCEPT THIS PRIVACY POLICY BY USING OUR PRODUCTS AND SERVICES ON OUR WEBSITE OR THROUGH ANY OTHER MEANS (COLLECTIVELY THE “SERVICES"). We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time by posting a revised version on our website. We will attempt to give a reasonable notice period upon making any changes; however, unless otherwise stated, the revised version will be effective at the time we post it.

## 1\. How Affirm collects your information.

#### 1.1. Information You Give Affirm.

If you open an account or use the Affirm Service, we may collect the following types of information: Personal information - your name, Social Security number, address, phone, email, third-party application IDs, and other similar information. Financial information - bank account numbers and/or credit card numbers that you link to your Affirm account or give us when you use the Services. Before permitting you to use the Services, we may require you to provide additional information, including but not limited to your date of birth, social security number and other personal information. We may use this information to verify your identity or other information you provide.

#### 1.2. Information Affirm Learns From Your Use.

When you visit the Affirm website or use the Services, we may collect information sent to us by your computer, mobile phone or any other device. This information may include your IP address, device information including but not limited to identifier, name and type, operating system, location, mobile network information and standard web log information, such as your browser type, traffic to and from our site, the pages you accessed on our website, and any other available information. We may also collect information about your use and interaction with our website, application or the Services. For example, we may evaluate your computer, mobile phone or other access device to identify any malicious software or activity that may affect the availability of the Services. When you use the Services, we may also store information based on your usage history. This includes, but is not limited to, details of your purchases, content you viewed, event information, click stream information, and cookies that may uniquely identify your browser or your account. We may also collect information about you from any contact you have with any of our services or employees, such as, with our customer support team, in surveys, or through interactions with our affiliates.

#### 1.3. Cookies and Anonymous Identifiers.

We use various technologies to collect and store information when you use the Services, and this may include sending one or more cookies or anonymous identifiers to your device. We also use cookies and anonymous identifiers when you interact with the services we offer to our partners, such as advertising services or Affirm features that may appear on other sites and in any other manner that we deem necessary for our business purposes.

#### 1.4. Information Obtained From Third Parties.

We may also obtain information about you from third parties such as credit bureaus and identity verification services. You may choose to provide us with access to certain personal information stored by third parties such as social media sites (such as Facebook and Twitter). The information we have access to varies by site and is controlled by your privacy settings on that site and your authorization. By associating an account managed by a third party with your Affirm account and authorizing Affirm to have access to this information, you agree that Affirm may collect, store and use this information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

## 2\. How Affirm protects your information.

#### 2.1. Safety Policies.

Affirm stores and processes your information maintaining physical, electronic and procedural safeguards. We maintain physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems and use safeguards such as firewalls and data encryption. We enforce physical access controls to our buildings, and we authorize access to personal information only for those employees or agents who require it to fulfill the responsibilities of their jobs.

## 3\. How Affirm uses your information.

#### 3.1. To Improve Our Service.

Affirm uses information to perform and improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for clients. For example, we may use information to provide customer service and support, process transactions, resolve disputes, collect payments, prevent illegal activities, customize the Services, reduce risk to all parties involved in our transactions, and verify the accuracy of information.

#### 3.2. To Serve Relevant Marketing to You.

We may use information to deliver targeted marketing, service update notices, and promotional offers based on your communication preferences. We may combine your information with information we collect from other companies and use it to improve and personalize the Services, content, and advertising.

#### 4.1. For Our Everyday Business Purposes.

We share your personal information with employees, affiliates, vendors, partners, merchant partners, marketing providers, and third parties as required to offer the Affirm Service. This includes, but is not limited to, processing transactions, maintaining your account, responding to court orders and legal investigations, litigation purposes, complying with audits or other investigations, and reporting to credit bureaus. We may share your information with the merchants you use the Affirm Services with for marketing purposes, and as otherwise permitted by law.

#### 4.2. When Required By Law.

We will share your information with any party when required by law or by a government request to do so or to combat fraud or criminal activity.

#### 4.3. With Our Merchant Partners to Provide Personalized Offers.

We may share your information with merchants you interact with using Affirm for marketing, if you consent or as permitted by law. For accounts created on or after 11/30/17: By creating an Affirm account, you consent to Affirm sharing your information with merchants you use the Affirm Services with, for those merchants to market to you. We do this to help merchants personalize services and offers, so you can have a better experience. You’re able to revoke your consent at any time by following the steps below. If you choose to do so, we will stop sharing your information with merchants from that point onward, except as necessary to complete transactions you initiate. To revoke your consent to information sharing with merchants for marketing, you can log into your Affirm account at www.affirm.com/u/ and edit your Personalized Services preferences.

## 5\. How Affirm does NOT use your information.

#### 5.1. Selling Information to Third Parties.

We don't sell or rent your personal information to third parties.

## 6\. What are your options?

#### 6.1. Notifications.

If you no longer wish to receive notifications about our Services, you may change your notification preferences by emailing help@affirm.com. Alternatively, you may be able to indicate your preference by logging into your account and adjusting your preferences or by following the directions provided with the communication. Affirm reserves the right to close or limit access to your account should you opt out of the crucial notices that are required to perform the Affirm Service. You are still responsible for any amounts due to Affirm even if we close or limit access to your account.

#### 6.2. SMS Messaging.

You can opt out of receiving SMS messages by emailing help@affirm.com. Alternatively, you may be able to indicate your preference by logging into your account and adjusting your preferences or by following the directions provided with the communication. Again, Affirm reserves the right to close or limit access to your account should you opt out of the crucial notices that are required to perform the Affirm Service. You are still responsible for any amounts due to Affirm even if we close or limit access to your account.

#### 6.3. Access Your Information.

You can review and edit your personal information at any time by logging in to your account on the Website or by contacting us at help@affirm.com. You can also request to close your account by contacting us at help@affirm.com. If you close your Affirm account, we will mark your account in our database as “Closed,” but will keep your account information in our database to comply with our legal obligations. This is necessary in order to deter fraud, by ensuring that persons who try to commit fraud will not be able to avoid detection simply by closing their account and opening a new account. If you close your account, your personally identifiable information will not be used by us for any further purposes, nor sold or shared with third parties, except as necessary to prevent fraud and assist law enforcement, as required by law or in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

#### 6.4. Contact Affirm.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, you should contact us at help@affirm.com.

Facts | What does Affirm, Inc. do with your personal information?  
---|---  
Why? |  Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.   
What? |  The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include: \- Social Security number and account balances  
\- Transaction history and account transactions  
\- Credit scores and checking account information  
When you are _no longer_ our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.   
How? |  All financial companies need to share customers' personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers' personal information; the reasons Affirm, Inc. chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.   
Reasons we can share your personal information | Does Affirm, Inc. share? | Can you limit this sharing?  
---|---|---  
**For our everyday business purposes--**   
such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus  | Yes | No  
**For our marketing purposes--**   
to offer our products and services to you  | Yes | No  
**For joint marketing with other financial companies** | No | We don't share  
**For our affiliates' everyday business purposes--**   
information about your transactions and experiences  | No | We don't share  
**For our affiliates' everyday business purposes--**   
information about your creditworthiness  | No | We don't share  
For nonaffiliates to market to you  | Yes | Yes  
To Limit Our Sharing |  You may limit our sharing by logging into your Affirm account at www.affirm.com/u/ and editing your Personalized Services preferences. 

Please note:  
If you are a _new_ customer, we can begin sharing your information 30 days from the date we sent this notice, or earlier if you consent or as permitted by law. When you are _no longer_ our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.  
However, you can contact us at any time to limit our sharing.   
  
---|---  
Questions? | Call 855-423-3729 or email help@affirm.com  
Who we are  
---  
**Who is providing this notice?** |  Affirm, Inc.   
What we do  
**How does Affirm, Inc. protect my personal information?** |  To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.   
**How does Affirm, Inc. collect my personal information?** |  We collect your personal information, for example, when you   
\- Apply for a loan or open an account   
\- Provide account information or pay your bills   
\- Use your credit or debit card   
We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.   
**Why can't I limit all sharing?** |  Federal law gives you the right to limit only   
\- sharing for affiliates' everyday business purposes--information about your creditworthiness   
\- affiliates from using your information to market to you   
\- sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you   
State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing. See below for more on your rights under state law.   
Definitions  
**Affiliates** |  Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.   
\- Affirm, Inc. does not share with our affiliates.   
**Nonaffiliates** |  Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.   
\- Nonaffiliates we can share with include our merchant partners and marketing service providers.   
**Joint marketing** |  A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.   
\- Affirm, Inc. doesn't jointly market.   
Other important information  
**Special Notice For State Residents**

For California Residents. We will not share personal information with affiliates or nonaffiliates except as permitted by California law, such as to process your transaction or with your consent. 

For Vermont Residents. We will not share personal information with affiliates or nonaffiliates except as permitted by Vermont law, such as to process your transaction or with your consent.   
  
Facts | What does Cross River Bank do with your personal information?  
---|---  
Why? |  Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.   
What? |  The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:  
\- Social Security number and Account balances  
\- Payment history and Transaction history  
\- Account transactions and Wire transfer instructions  
When you are _no longer_ our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.   
How? |  All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers’ personal information; the reasons Cross River Bank chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.   
Reasons we can share your personal information | Does Cross River Bank share? | Can you limit this sharing?  
---|---|---  
**For our everyday business purposes—**  
such as to process your transactions, maintain your accounts, respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus  | Yes | No  
**For our marketing purposes—**  
to offer our products and services to you  | Yes | No  
**For joint marketing with other financial companies** | Yes | No  
**For our affiliates' everyday business purposes—**  
information about your transactions and experiences  | No | We don't share  
**For our affiliates' everyday business purposes—**  
information about your creditworthiness  | No | We don't share  
For nonaffiliates to market to you  | No | We don't share  
Questions? | Call toll-free 1-877-55CRB55 or go to www.crossriverbank.com  
---|---  
What we do  
---  
**How does Cross River Bank protect my personal information?** |  To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.   
We also maintain other physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect this information and we limit access to information to those employees for whom access is appropriate.   
**How does Cross River Bank collect my personal information?** |  We collect your personal information, for example, when you   
\- Open an account or Apply for a loan   
\- Make deposits or withdrawals from your account or Provide employment information   
\- Give us your contact information   
We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.   
**Why can't I limit all sharing?** |  Federal law gives you the right to limit only   
\- sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes-information about your creditworthiness   
\- affiliates from using your information to market to you   
\- sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you   
State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing. See below for more on your rights under state law.   
Definitions  
**Affiliates** |  Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.   
_\- Cross River Bank does not share with our affiliates._  
**Nonaffiliates** |  Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.   
_\- Nonaffiliates we share with can include loan finance companies._  
**Joint marketing** |  A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.   
_\- Our joint marketing partner(s) include loan finance companies._  
**Other important information**  
**Special Notice For State Residents**

**For Alaska, Illinois, Maryland and North Dakota Customers.** We will not share personal information with nonaffiliates either for them to market to you or for joint marketing-without your authorization. 

**For California Customers.** We will not share personal information with nonaffiliates either for them to market to you or for joint marketing-without your authorization. We will also limit our sharing of personal information about you with our affiliates to comply with all California privacy laws that apply to us. 

**For Massachusetts, Mississippi and New Jersey Customers.** We will not share personal information from deposit or share relationships with nonaffiliates either for them to market to you or for joint marketing-without your authorization. 

**For Vermont Customers.** We will not disclose information about your creditworthiness to our affiliates and will not disclose your personal information, financial information, credit report, or health information to nonaffiliated third parties to market to you, other than as permitted by Vermont law, unless you authorize us to make those disclosures. Additional information concerning our privacy policies can be found at www.crossriverbank.comor call 1-877-55CRB55.
